recipebliss.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Recipe Bliss

Net 90, LLC knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Net 90, LLC’s treatment of personal information that Net 90, LLC gathers when you are on the Net 90, LLC website and when you use Net 90, LLC services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Net 90, LLC does not own or control, or to individuals that Net 90, LLC does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by Net 90, LLC

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Net 90, LLC users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Net 90, LLC and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Net 90, LLC cookie information, and the page you requested. Net 90, LLC uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.  
Net 90, LLC may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.  
Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Net 90, LLC will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

E-mail Communications

Net 90, LLC is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the ”Sharing Your Information” section below. Net 90, LLC may send out e-mails with RecipeBliss.com – related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Net 90, LLC cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The ”help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Net 90, LLC’s coolest features.

Third Party Advertising – Ad Choices

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Sharing Your Information

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

RecipeBliss.com Personnel: RecipeBliss.com personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Net 90, LLC business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Net 90, LLC, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of Net 90, LLC and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Net 90, LLC, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: Net 90, LLC allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Net 90, LLC website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and “opt-out” procedures of our third-party ad servers, please contact us at [info@netninety.com](mailto://info@netninety.com "Opt Out Procedures").

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Children Under 18 Years of Age

You must be 13 years and older to register to use RecipeBliss.com website. As a result, Net 90, LLC does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Net 90, LLC has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using Net 90, LLC or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Net 90, LLC may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Net 90, LLC website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the RecipeBliss.com website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to thisPrivacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 25, 2013 and last updated July 25, 2013.
